Previously
on Two and a Half Men...
I am gonna ask Lyndsey
to marry me.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will marry you!
I was wondering if you'd do me
the honor of being my best man.
What?
Larry, where can
I put this poop?
This is my sister Gretchen.
She just moved here.
Gretchen, this is
Jeff Strongman.
I think the computer
just read his thoughts.
(squealing)
(laughs)
Yes!
The guy I had dinner with
last night offered me
a job in San Francisco.
Where does that leave us?
I have to take this.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I'm here for you.
If you wanted to go with her...
Oh, thank God.
I thought
about what you said
I don't want
to work for Google.
I want to stay and work
with you.
We're gonna do great things
together.
All right.
So where do I sleep?
♪ Men. ♪
Uh...
hello?
Oh, hey.
Jake?
Barry.
Did you break into this house
and kill Walden?
'Cause if you did, just know...
I'm one hell of a roommate.
No, I'm a friend
of Walden's.
I'm gonna be crashing
here for a few days.
Actually, Walden would probably
say I'm his best friend.
Oh, really?
'Cause I have a picture
of us at Splash Mountain
that refutes that statement.
What's that you're cooking?
Cinnamon French toast;
Walden's favorite.
Walden's allergic to cinnamon.
No, Walden is allergic
to nutmeg.
Touché.
What's his birthday,
favorite color and worst fear?
July 12, forest green,
dying in your arms.
Coffee? Cream,
two Splendas?
Wait, y-you know
what I like, too?
I know a lot of things.
I know that you're sleeping
with Lyndsey,
who is engaged to Larry,
who thinks
you're Jeff Strongman,
and you just went on a date
with Gretchen, Larry's sister.
And your worst fear
is not dying in this house.
(gasps)
Witch.
Get out of my head.
Something smells good.
That is the cinnamon
French tatas.
Hey, you-you must be Jake.
Give your cousin Jenny a hug.
That's not Jake.
Shut up, Dad.
Morning!
Hey, Berta.
Welcome home, Jake.
That's not Jake.
That's Walden's friend Barry.
Uh, Berta,
making a special batch
of French toast for you
topped with a dollop
of marijuana butter.
I like "Not Jake."
All right,
who wants the first batch?
(others clamoring)
Aw, hell, no.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x17 ♪
Welcome Home, Jake
Original Air Date on March 13, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Extra! Extra!
Alan boards the Titanic!
Read all about it!
You're just jealous.
Jealous of what?
Your up-and-coming role
in the Newsies remake?
I will have you know that
the salesgirl at Goodwill said
that I look dashing.
Why are you wearing this outfit?
I'm going out
with Gretchen again tonight.
As her date or her caddie?
Oh, that reminds me-- I gotta
get a cover for my wood.
Why are you going out
with her again?
What do you mean?
I like her, she likes me--
honestly, I can see myself
spending the rest
of Jeff Strongman's life
with her.
Okay, unlike Jeff Strongman,
she is a real person.
With real feelings.
And real... (grunts)
I know, I know. I...
I don't want to hurt her.
If that's the case,
then you need to walk away.
I-I will, I will. You're right.
Right after I have sex with her.
No!
Well, I'm not gonna walk away
while I'm having sex with her.
That would be rude.
Hey, Jeff Strongman
looks good in that hat.
Top of the day to you, too, sir.
Wait, you can tell
when he's not Alan?
Oh, yeah. I mean,
Jeff exudes a quiet confidence,
whereas
Alan just...
exudes.
Is there a shower I can use?
Uh, oh, yeah.
Uh, Alan's room's
down the hall on the left.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
What about Jenny's?
She's in there with Brooke.
Yeah, I don't think I can go
in there again "by accident."
But-but, uh,
wh-what about your bathroom?
They're all my bathrooms!
Alan's shower.
Great.
Uh...
so, is this
a "pee in the shower"
or "not pee in the shower"
household?
"Not pee in the shower."
So it's a "pee in the shower
and lie about it" household.
And don't touch
my shower porn!
That stuff took a long time
to laminate.
Everything... you...
say... is... weird.
Look, look, I know you're upset
about Barry moving in with us,
but hitting me
with a 25-cent hat
is not gonna solve anything.
He's not moving in.
He's just staying here
for a couple days
while we brainstorm
some new tech ideas.
Oh, Walden,
you're such a pushover.
Somebody else said they were
only gonna stay in the house
for a few days. Remember that?
Oh, believe me,
I remember.
And now, here we are,
four months later,
and Jenny's still living
with us.
Why... can't... you...
hear... yourself?
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Summer lovin',
had me a blast ♪
♪ Summer lovin' ♪
♪ Happened so fa-ast ♪
♪ I met a girl
crazy for me ♪
♪ Met a boy cute as can be ♪
Maybe we should start again.
Why, was I pitchy?
You are so adorable.
Oh, and you have broccoli
in your teeth.
Oh... (chuckles)
You want to get it for me?
Ooh, a kiss and a free meal.
Mmm...!
Yum.
(chuckles)
I've never had broccoli
and tongue before.
I gotta say,
I love that hat on you.
Oh!
You know, it's funny, I gave one
just like that to Goodwill.
Yeah, yeah,
this is the same one.
(both laugh)
Well, uh,
thanks again for dinner tonight.
Oh, yeah.
Next one's on you, though.
Absolutely.
Um, speaking of which,
I'm not sure we should keep
seeing each other.
What? We don't have
to go somewhere expensive.
Oh, God,
you're making this so hard.
That's what he said!
Oh, peas, pod.
No, it's... (sighs)
it's just, you know,
I'm Larry's best man
and you're his sister.
I mean, what if things go wrong
and we screw up the wedding?
Look, I like you
and I think you like me,
and if it'll make you
more comfortable,
we can keep it a secret for now.
I mean, if you're good
at keeping secrets.
I don't know.
"Strongman" in German
means "honest man."
Is that true?
Jawohl.
But I suppose
we could keep it...
(German accent):
under ze radar.
Great.
Hmm...
So you know, uh...
Larry and Lyndsey are in
Palm Springs for the weekend.
They are?
Yeah.
You want to... come inside?
BOTH:
That's what she said!
(laughing)
♪ Men. ♪
(sirens wailing on TV)
This is awesome.
(laughing)
These are the best graphics
I've ever seen.
(laughs)
Uh-oh!
The cops shot my tires out.
Now I'm runnin'.
Oh...
Wait, this isn't a video game.
(laughing): We're watching a car
chase on the news.
(laughing)
Oh.
So I probably didn't
score that three-pointer
to win the Laker game, either.
Are you sure
you're not Jake?
I'm not sure.
Hey, are you guys
really lesbians?
Or are you like
those "lesbian" from Craigslist
that came over and tied me up
and stole my laptop?
(laughing)
If we weren't,
would we do this?
Okay, brain,
you are high,
but I need you
to remember this.
Forget calculus
if you have to.
WALDEN:
Hey.
Nobody heard the pizza guy
at the door?
I told you we wouldn't
have to get up.
Told you we wouldn't
have to pay for it.
Is this all you guys have
been doing the whole day?
No, we spent an hour
trying to find
where you hid your bong.
Which knocked me
into overtime, FYI.
Walden, I am loving it here.
I mean, pizza, lesbians,
weed scavenger hunts...
Nobody paying rent...
It just keeps getting better.
Hey, Barry, can I talk
to you for a second?
WOMEN:
Ooh, you're in trouble!
(laughing)
Is this why you're here?
Just to hang out and get high
and eat pizza?
I feel like this is
a trick question.
'Cause I thought you were here
to work on a new
project with me.
No, no, no, I am!
I am. Okay, okay,
check out this idea:
So I was watching Brooke
and Jenny make out earlier,
and I thought to myself,
what if we filmed lesbians
doing stuff to each other...
and then we put that
on the Internet?
How has no one thought of that?
I know!
You know what?
It's too late for them.
They're a lost cause.
We can hear you.
I will give any
of you... $100.
All you have to do
is come up here
and take it from me.
Later.
Nah, I'm fine. - Nah.
Do you see that?
Don't be them!
I only let
you stay here
for a few days
to help you transition.
Okay, okay.
I got another idea.
Uh... bacon-flavored eggs.
All me and you
got to figure out
is how to make the chicken
and the pig have sex.
Well, maybe you could show 'em
the lesbian porn.
Wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
What if you got
the chickens drunk?
Would that work?
I've gotten laid a lot
by getting chicks drunk.
(laughing)
Hey, Berta,
what about you?
You ever been
with a woman?
Have you?
There you are.
Get down off that couch,
you naughty boy.
(whimpering)
Ooh, a quarter.
Hey, this hat
just paid for itself.
Give me that.
Drop it.
(growling, muttering)
Ruh-roh.
♪ Men. ♪
So, how was Palm Springs?
What the hell's
going on here?
It-it isn't what
it looks like.
It looks like you're having
kinky sex with my sister.
Then it is what it looks like.
I can't
believe this.
Me, neither.
This is the best
day of my life!
What?!
What guy doesn't want to see
his best friend bang his sister?
What?!
What?! What?!
My two favorite people in
the world got together.
Those are your two
favorite people?
Don't worry.
You're number three.
If you were banging my
sister, you'd be number one.
Well, I'm-I'm glad
you're so excited about this.
I was worried you were gonna
punch me in the face.
Ah, if anything, I'd maybe
swat you on the nose with
a rolled-up newspaper.
Or cut off your balls.
Well, I'm gonna go
get dressed.
I have to take Jeff
for a walk.
Hey, you know
that special bottle of champagne
we were saving
for our wedding?
Let's pop it now!
Why not? I just popped
your sister five minutes ago.
Jeff, you are the king!
Really? What are you doing
with Larry's sister?
Just a little game.
You know, I-I pretend
I'm a dog, and she rescues me,
and then I give her my bone.
All right, Alan,
you know what? Stop.
Stop being friends
with my fiancé,
stop dating my fiancé's sister,
and stop poking me on Facebook.
It doesn't mean what
you think it does.
You know what?
You can't tell me what to do.
I am my own man.
I will do what I want
with whomever I want
whenever I want.
Now, excuse me.
(groans)
You're standing on my leash.
♪ Men. ♪
♪ All the single Barrys,
all the single Barrys ♪
♪ Make a turkey sandwich,
make a turkey sandwich ♪
♪ If you like it then you should
have put some cheese on it ♪
♪ May-a-o, oh-oh-oh,
oh-oh-oh, oh... ♪
Oh, hey.
Bare, can I talk to you?
Sure. What's up?
Let me ask you something.
Suppose you had someone
living with you,
and you wanted them to leave.
How would you go about
making that clear?
Well, I don't like
confrontation,
so I'd probably do something
passive-aggressive
like sit them down
and ask them
how they would approach...
Oh, you're asking me
to move out.
No, no, no, no, I'm not
asking you to move out.
I'm-I'm asking you
to move in...
to the... outside.
Okay.
Boy, man, I'm so sorry.
I just have been having a lot
of fun here, you know.
Everybody's so nice,
and you've been so welcoming.
Up until just now when you
told me to get the hell out.
Don't get me wrong.
It's not that I don't love
having you here.
It's just that I don't think
that I can legally
have anyone else live here
unless I adopt them.
I'm down for that.
Okay, well, let's table that,
but in-in the meantime, we'll
look for an apartment for you.
Uh, well, I mean,
today is kind of already shot.
Maybe pick it up tomorrow?
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
I mean, it's-it's 10:30.
In the morning.
Great.
Uh, I'm gonna go get high
and eat my sandwich
out on the deck.
Okay
He's never moving out.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Wait. Are you just getting back
from your date with Gretchen?
No. No, no. I had to go back
to the restaurant.
I left my hat
at the valet stand.
Liar!
You would never pay for parking.
All right, admit it,
you slept with Gretchen.
You're right, I slept with her.
And I found a broken meter
two blocks from the restaurant.
I thought you were
calling it off with her.
Well, I started to, but
you-you know how breakups go.
I mean, you try
to be considerate
and let her down easy,
and next thing you know,
you're wearing a dog collar
and a leash
while she lets you
lick peanut butter
out of a chew toy
between her boobs.
♪ Men. ♪
Whoa...
Look at this place.
Hello, apartment,
good-bye panties, huh?
I don't think
this place is for me.
It just doesn't scream "Barry."
It will
when the panties come off.
No. Plus, the feng shui
is just off.
All right.
This is the sixth place
you didn't like.
And the last one you said was
in a bad school district.
What's going on here?
Nothing. Nothing's
going on. I just...
I've never really
lived alone before.
Never?
Well, when my dad left,
I lived with my mom,
and then boarding school,
and then, in college,
I always had roommates,
and then after college,
I lived with Nicole.
I mean,
I'm like a baby duck, Walden.
When Mama Duck leaves, I cling
to the next mama duck.
Okay, but my flock is too big,
so, you gotta get the flock
out of my house.
I don't know
if I can make it on my own.
Okay, listen, I know
what's going on.
I know how you feel.
I felt the same way when
my wife walked out on me.
What did you do?
I bought a house
and let a 45-year-old man
and his son live there.
Wow. A real
Scared Straight moment here.
Let's grab up a pizza
on the way back to the beach.
Barry, listen to me.
I'm going to say
something to you
that I have never
said before in my life.
You can't live with me.
Oh, my God.
(laughing)
I did it.
I'm sorry.
You're-You're my first.
No, no, no,
I don't want to be your first.
Your first should be
someone special,
like a whore
that your stepdad buys you.
...is an example I just made up.
Listen, Barry, you're...
you are gonna be okay.
And you can come and visit
anytime that you want.
Really?
Yeah, just stop on by.
But you can't live with me!
Now or ever.
Okay, but I can't just
stay here.
Yes, you can!
I'm gonna take care
of the paperwork,
and then
I'll send your stuff over.
You just make yourself at home.
But you can't live with me!
All right, message received.
Okay, I'm sorry--
I'm just... I'm really excited.
This is a big moment for me.
I'm gonna go find Alan.
You can't live with me!
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
But you can't
live with me!
♪ Men. ♪
I can't tell you how happy I am
you guys are dating.
(laughs)
No offense, Sis, but some of
the guys you've brought home--
I mean, no job,
no house, no car.
Real losers.
Wow, sounds like the deadbeats
I used to date
before I found Larry.
Well, I've, uh, I've had some
real winners in my past, too.
Cheaters, drunks,
45-year-old women
trying to pass as 38.
Lyndsey just turned 38!
Well, luckily, those people
are out of our lives now.
Yeah, but sometimes I swear
I can see their stupid faces
right in front of me.
That might be
a wine-induced hallucination.
Speaking of wine,
a toast to the four of us.
May this be the first
of many dinners, celebrations,
holidays, vacations,
anniversaries...
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, we get it.
To us. Bottoms up.
(Alan chuckles)
I know mine will be.
Mmm! You are a bad girl.
(chuckles)
(clears her throat)
I think we're making
them uncomfortable.
Not as uncomfortable
as last night,
having sex with your butt
on a hot stove.
We were fooling
around in the kitchen,
and I picked him up
in a moment of passion.
(laughs)
I loved it.
LARRY:
Wow!
Lyndsey doesn't use the stove
for cooking or sex.
Sweetie, sweetie,
what are you doing?
Don't forget the little butter packets.
Oh!
You're my little butter packet.
Oh.
(chuckles)
Doesn't look
like they're thinking
about any of their exes now.
No, it doesn't.
He's thinking
about banging my sister.
I know what he's thinking!
♪ Men. ♪
Okay.
One roommate down,
two to go.
Alan...
Hey, there he is.
Barry?
What are you doing here?
Well, you said I could stop
by anytime I wanted, so...
Yeah, but I-I just left you.
17 minutes ago.
I know.
I missed you, too.
Walden, are you done?
We're in the middle of a game.
Hey, can you go
on a beer run?
What the hell is going on here?
This is my house!
BERTA:
Do you mind?!
Some of us are trying to nap!
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, oh, well, then put up
a sign that says
only one roll of mints
per customer.
(door closes)
Oh.
Lyndsey.
Are you waiting?
Someone pooping in there?
What the hell was that about?
(imitating Gretchen): "You're my
little butter packet."
What upset you more?
That she stole that bread...
or my heart?
So you are doing this
just to make me jealous.
No, that's not it at all.
Too bad, 'cause it's working.
I'm sorry, I...
No, I-I really like Gretchen.
I-I can't do this.
Jeff Strongman can't.
But Alan Harper can.
Works for me.
(both moaning)
Is that a roll of mints
in your pocket
or are you just
happy to see me?
Actually,
it is a roll of mints.
And a comb.
And a bottle of Paco Rabanne.
♪ Men. ♪
All right, the shot
for the win.
Be the ball, see the cups.
Hey, Barry, check
out these cups.
Aah! Ball to the face.
First time for everything.
I may need to see that
again and again.
Walden, we have
security cameras, right?
Where's Walden?
(music soundtrack playing on TV)
I could totally live here.
(laughs)
Screech, will you never learn?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man